不，不要……
不要啊！
宇宙洗衣房
Excuse me?
打扰一下好吗？
Excuse me, sir?
打扰一下好吗，先生？
打扰一下好吗？
Oh, come on.
哦，拜托
Do you have a moment, sir?
有空吗，先生？
I'm kind of in the middle of something here.
的确有点事儿在忙
Yes? Thank you.
不劳您费心
I've come a long way for you, Franck.
我可是大老远过来找你的，弗兰克
My name is Victor.
我叫维克托
Hi.
嗨
And you are....
你就是……
You are Franck.
你就是弗兰克吧
You are so much more than just a sheep, aren't you?
一张羊皮岂能容下你的伟大灵魂，对吧？
Oh yeah? How would you know?
哦是吗？你咋知道的？
Look at you. You're an adventurer, Franck.
看看你自己，天生就是冒险家啊，弗兰克
Just like me, you're... a lone wolf.
你和我一样，就像是一匹孤狼
Tell me, does one choose to be alone?
你说说看，有谁会甘心寂寞吗？
No, one doesn't.
没人会的
One doesn’t even choose to be a wolf.
人们甚至连狼都不想做
Or does one?
不是吗？
Well, mister... err... Hector.
我说你这位……赫克托先生
Victor. Victor.
维克多，维克多
I don’t know what you’re on about
我不知道你想干什么
but I'm just
a sheep minding its own business.
但是呢，本羊从不管别人的事
And I suggest you do the same.
奉劝你也一样
No. No no no, Franck. Wait wait wait.
别，别别别，弗兰克，等等
No. This is not... the way.
别，别这样
Just give me one minute of your precious time.
我只占用你宝贵的一分钟时间
Precious time?
宝贵的时间？
Hehehe.
我笑了哈
Yeah just give me one minute.
嗯，给我一分钟就好
You would have one more minute, wouldn't you?
一分钟时间你还是有的，对吗？
Okay half.
好吧，半分钟
Half a minute.
就半分钟
I knew it.
我就知道
You will not regret this.
你不会后悔踏上这条
The adventures you will have.
即将到来的冒险之旅的
All the lives you've ever wanted.
你梦寐以求的各种生活
All you’ve been missing.
还有你错过的一切
Here. This is... the best product we have... in store.
喏，这是我们店里最好的产品
Variable spin speed, excellent tumble performance...
转速可调，翻滚性能优异
...in one... handy... device. Squeaky clean.
这个小装置全都能搞定，而且绝对干净
Well this... this better be good.
好吧，最好管用
Took me ages to tie that rope.
我花了很久才系上那根绳子
With my fucking hooves.
用我那该死的蹄子
No more need for hooves.
不需要用蹄子的
No more sheepy business.
不需要再像羊那样
Ho! Time flies.
嚯！这么快就到时间了
Wait wait wait wait wait wait.
等等 等等 等等……
How does this thing work?
这东西有啥用？
I mean, how do I make it work?
我是说，我该怎么使用它？
No you don't.
不，你不用管
I just turned it on for you.
我已经帮你启动了
When can I go?
我什么时候能走？
Where can I go?
我又能去哪呢？
We will pick you up. Don't worry,
我们会接你的，放心好了
just stay here.
待在这里就好
In this exact place.
原地不动
Don't move. Just wait.
别动哦，等着吧
That's it?
这样就行了？
Hey!
嘿！
Wait, mister!
等等，你这位！
Eh, Casper!
呃，叫卡死脖的先生！
Hector whatever!
还是赫克托什么的！